Narrator: Breakfast
Speaker: bread
Narrator: 12
Speaker: butter
Narrator: 7
Speaker: cereal
Narrator: 1
Speaker: cheese
Narrator: 6
Speaker: coffee
Narrator: 11
Speaker: eggs
Narrator: 3
Speaker: jam
Narrator: 4
Speaker: juice
Narrator: 8
Speaker: milk
Narrator: 10
Speaker: sugar
Narrator: 2
Speaker: tea
Narrator: 5
Narrator: toast
Narrator: Lunch or dinner
Speaker: fish, for example salmon, tuna
Narrator: 17
Speaker: herbs
Narrator: 15
Speaker: meat, for example chicken, sausages, steak, ham
Narrator: 14
Speaker: oil
Narrator: 21
Speaker: pasta
Narrator: 27
Speaker: rice
Narrator: 26
Speaker: salad
Narrator: 23
Speaker: seafood
Narrator: 28
Speaker: spices
Narrator: Vegetables
Speaker: carrots
Narrator: 16
Speaker: chips
Narrator: 13
Speaker: a lettuce
Narrator: 30
Speaker: mushrooms
Narrator: 20
Speaker: onions
Narrator: 24
Speaker: peas
Narrator: 19
Speaker: peppers
Narrator: 22
Speaker: potatoes
Narrator: 25
Speaker: tomatoes
Narrator: Fruit
Speaker: apples
Narrator: 39
Speaker: bananas
Narrator: 35
Speaker: oranges
Narrator: 32
Speaker: a pineapple
Narrator: 36
Speaker: strawberries
Narrator: Desserts
Speaker: cake
Narrator: 38
Speaker: fruit salad
Narrator: 33
Speaker: ice cream
Narrator: Snacks
Speaker: biscuits
Narrator: 42
Speaker: chocolate
Narrator: 34
Speaker: crisps
Narrator: 40
Speaker: nuts
Narrator: 31
Speaker: a sandwich
Narrator: 44
Speaker: sweets